It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
That day, I felt a little more sexy.
あの日なんか色っぽくなったんですけど
I don't think so.
そんなことないと思います
Is there not?
ないかな?
It's changed live though.
ライブでも変わったけどね
Is that what Shaq looks like?
シャックそういう感じなの?
It's always like this.
いつもこんな感じです
Her style is beautiful.
彼女のスタイル綺麗だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You don't exercise much, do you?
あんま運動しないんじゃっけ?
I was playing soccer.
サッカーやってました
How much?
どれくらい?
About 3 years.
3年くらい
You already did it, right?
もう今、したでしょ?
Now, but you can still do it.
今は、でも今でもできますよ
To do it.
や ることには
What about your position?
ポジションはどうですか?
It's a forward.
フォワードです
That's amazing.
すごいね
What are you good at?
何が得意?
He was very fast.
めっちゃ足速かったです
Is it surprising?
意外ですか?
It's because I have long legs.
足長いからね
It's been a long time alone.
一人で長いもんね
Is that so?
そうですかね?
One distance.
距離が一つ
It seems like it's a step different here.
ここ一歩違いそうだね
Not really.
そうでもない
The type that ran like hell.
めちゃめちゃ走ってたタイプ
Skip one more step.
もう一歩飛ばして
myself here.
自分がここで
What's it like at night?
夜はどうなんですか?
What about at night?
夜は?
Relatively normal.
割と普通
Are you the type to try it yourself?
自分がやってみるタイプ?
no.
いや
What is that question?
何その質問?
Become a defenseman?
ディフェンスになる?
I guess it won't happen.
ならないですね
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
I haven't been asked many questions.
あんまり質問されたことないです
Are you the confessing type?
告白するタイプか?
Maybe it's the type of thing that happens.
されるタイプかも
I would never do it myself.
自分から絶対しないです
Please back.
後ろにしてください
Maybe she's the type to be confessed to.
告白されるタイプかも
I'm not really good at chasing,
なんか、追うのがあんまり得意じゃなくて、
I'm not interested in people.
人に興味ない
I can see it, but today.
見えてるんだけど、今日
Did you have Conticton?
コンティクトン持ってたの?
What do you think?
どうなんですかね?
It's a normal tantsu.
普通のタンツです
I thought it was just going up.
上がってるだけだと思ってた
I don't wear them anymore.
もう、 履いてないよ
since
自
In minutes
分 で、
Are you wearing a wai?
ワ イは付けてる?
No, I don't think it's attached.
いや、付けてないと思います
Well, I'm putting it on.
じゃあ、付けてます
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
I can see it.
見えちゃってる
How did you fall in love with Love?
どうやってラブの恋をしたの?
Mail order?
通販?
I don't buy much at the store.
あんまり、お店で買わない
Well then, if you can reach it, if you feel like it,
じゃあ、もう、 手に届いたら、気が出たら、
It turned out like this.
こんなのになっちゃった
It's pretty amazing.
だいぶ凄いよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Make it a wall.
壁にして
The top is already a little big.
もう、上は、 ちょっとサイズ大きい
The one above?
上とそっちが?
together.
一緒
Why can I see it here?
なんでここ見えちゃうの?
Is this working?
これじゃってる?
Have you been using it for quite a while?
結構長く使ってる?
Since it's from overseas, it's a bit quiet, isn't it?
海外のだから、 ちょっと、ちゃっちんですよね
So, when I made my selection above, I ended up with something like this.
じゃあ、上で選んだら、 こんなのになっちゃった
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
A little cute, isn't it?
ちょっと、可愛いじゃないですか、
this.
これ
How did I get it to look like this underneath?
どうやったら、下もこんな感じだったの?
I can't.
できないよ
It gets dangerous after a while though
だいぶしたら、ヤバいけど
hey.
ね
That's not the case though.
そんな ことないですけど
There it is.
そのある
only.
ほんの
In your hand.
手に
Have you ever been told that?
言われたことあるでしょ?
Well, there is.
まあ、あるわ
I've never been told that.
言われたことない
How do you feel?
どういう気持ち?
What do you mean?
どういうの?
difficult.
難しい
On the contrary, that's the only thing I can see.
逆に、そこだけ見えてんだね
By yourself?
自分で?
I want to expand it myself.
自分で広げてみたい
By yourself.
自分で
how?
どう やって?
Looks good on you.
似合って
It suits you.
似合ってるんですよね
difficult.
難しい
interesting.
面白い
Stretch it out again.
もう一回伸ばして
how was it?
どうだった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかったです